<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Strawberry</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_tab_home">home</string>
    <string name="home_tab_cate">category</string>
    <string name="home_tab_shopbag">shopbag</string>
    <string name="home_tab_me">me</string>
    <string name="home_search">search</string>
    <string name="setting_safe">account and safe</string>
    <string name="setting_msg">message</string>
    <string name="setting_language">language</string>
    <string name="setting_address">address</string>
    <string name="setting_email">email</string>
    <string name="setting_suggest">suggest</string>
    <string name="setting_clear">clear</string>
    <string name="setting_version">version</string>
    <string name="setting_about">about strawberry net</string>
    <string name="setting_logout">logout</string>
    <string name="setting_name">your name</string>
    <string name="setting_nick">your nick</string>
    <string name="title_setting">setting</string>

    <string name="digits_num_en">1234567890qwertyuiopasdfghjklzxcvbnm</string>
    <string name="checkout_idcard_title">The identity card or passport number of the subscribers of the customs declaration materials in China</string>
    <string name="checkout_idcard">·For the Chinese April 12, 2016 of the General Administration of Customs on cross-border e-commerce retail import and export commodities related to regulatory matters announcement \n where the electronic commerce enterprises to buy cross-border e-commerce retail imports (ordering) personal identity information verification, and provide the Customs by the competent department of the state certified identity information effectively \n all web delivery of strawberry to Chinese domestic shopping orders, related cross-border tax would be absorbed by strawberry net e-commerce enterprises, if the guests are required to pay the tax please contact customer service to confirm with the strawberry net</string>
    <string name="checkout_coupon">·You need to input the discount code correctly (hint: you can use the copy paste function) \n. Each discount code is only used once. \n discount code can not be used together with the whole network discount, for example, the total discount is 10 percent off or the perfume product is folded up to 10 percent off and so on \n. This offer is only limited to the specific brand or product. Please check the concessionary terms again</string>
</resources>
